const quiz = [
  {
    id: '1',
    question: 'WHICH PLANET HAS THE LARGEST ASTEROID BELT',
    option1: 'Saturn',
    option2: 'Venus',
    option3: 'Jupiter',
    option4: 'Mars',
    answer: 'Saturn',
  },
  {
    id: '2',
    question:
      "If you were to enter a black hole, there would be a white hole on the other side. Why is it impossible to get out of the white hole after entering?",
    option1: "White holes don't exist",
    option2: 'Einstein Rosen Bridge',
    option3: 'Hole will close off',
    option4:'Time travel',
    answer: 'Time travel',
  },
  {
    id: '3',
    question: 'Which female astronaut spent the maximum time in space?',
    option1: 'Lisa Norwak',
    option2: 'Kalpana Chawla',
    option3: 'Sunita Chawla',
    option4: 'None of these',
    answer: 'Kalpana Chawla',
  },
  {
    id: '4',
    question: 'An astronaut in outer space will observe sky as',
    option1: 'Blue',
    option2: 'Black',
    option3: 'White',
    option4: 'Red',
    answer: 'Black',
  },
  {
    id: '5',
    question:
      "Which of the following planets rotates in a direction opposite to the direction of earth's rotation?",
    option1: 'Mars',
    option2: 'Jupiter',
    option3: 'Venus',
    option4: 'Mercury',
    answer: 'Venus',
  },
  {
    id: '6',
    question: 'The planets on either side of the earth are _______ & _______:',
    option1: 'Mercury and Venus',
    option2: 'Mars and Jupiter',
    option3: 'Mars and Venus',
    option4: 'Venus and Saturn',
    answer: 'Mars and Venus',
  },
  {
    id: '7',
    question: "When a star is 'red shifted' , it means the star is___________.",
    option1: 'Shifting away from the Earth',
    option2: 'Shifting towards the Earth',
    option3: 'Shifting left of the Earth',
    option4: 'Shifting right of the Earth',
    answer: 'Shifting away from the Earth',
  },
  {
    id: '8',
    question: 'How does a solar sail move?',
    option1: 'Using dark matter',
    option2: 'Using wind in space',
    option3: "Using sun's energy",
    option4: "The sun's dark spots",
    answer: "Using sun's energy",
  },
  {
    id: '9',
    question:
      'Although white dwarf stars are small in size, they are the most______.',
    option1: 'Coldest',
    option2: 'Active',
    option3: 'Dense',
    option4: 'Hottest',
    answer: 'Dense',
  },
  {
    id: '10',
    question: 'Neutron Stars can spin about',
    option1: '20 times/sec',
    option2: '170 times/sec',
    option3: '360 times/sec',
    option4: '600 times/sec',
    answer: '600 times/sec',
  },
];

export default quiz;
